No living creature was
harmed during the filming.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
If they know we are here...
they'll go to Turgut Bey for it.
There were soldiers running
up, my bey.
Alps! For Turgut Bey!
Attack!
Come on!
You will pay for your betrayal!
If I was with you,
that would be the real treason.
Don't you still understand,
Rogatus?
Against the weasels, all
wolves unite.
They stand together!
You won't get out of here!
Neither dead or alive.
You should only survive
until Osman comes.
Soldier! You did well by
watching him.
I knew that Turks can't be trusted.
We are here, Turgut Bey!
Come here!
There will be more soldiers, my bey.
My bey, my bey, we need to leave!
My bey, they are coming!
Come on! My bey!
My bey, this way!
Move! Get them!
Open it!
Come on, alps!
Crouch!
Kill them!
They are out of arrows!
Open it!
I won't leave the Turkmen kids!
I'll return. For the kids and
your head, I'll return.
Attack!
Come on!
They are going to the secret passage!
Break it! Break it!
Open it!
Hit it!
Come on, alps!
Open it!
Cerkutay!
Come on!
Hold it, brother!
Open this! Open it!
Allahu Akbar.
Come on. Mashalah.
Come on.
Open it!
Move out! Move out!
We couldn't get the kids.
What will we do, Osman Bey?
My warriors are nimble.
They left marks.
They are going to the abbey.
So will we.
But not now. There is time.
Return to your tribe.
So be it.
Osman even knows the secret
passages in my castle!
And what are you doing?
What are you doing?
You should thank God that
he couldn't take the kids.
Otherwise, I would break every
one of your skulls...
one by one.
I sent Bahadır after Gökçe.
I want you to ask the women.
There surely be something to follow.
They are shrewd.
They must've seen something.
Don't worry.
I trust you, Aygül.
Together, we'll find the traitor.
Inshallah.
When did the Kayı tribe ever
held a traitor?
Malhun Hatun.
It will be revealed.
Bala.
Ayşe told me.
You didn't eat anything.
Don't be like this, my girl.
I'm hurt, mother.
Gonca flied away.
Ahmed is on the heathens' hands.
Osman didn't return.
He will.
Of course, he will!
He will return with Ahmed!
Inshallah, mother.
Inshallah.
Osman!
Don't be grieved.
Our warriors left tracks.
We know where are they taken to.
Thank Allah.
Mashallah to my lions.
Where are they, Osman Bey?
They are taken to Hristo Abbey, brother.
Cerkutay must be there already.
After he scouts the place,
we'll take our children back.
Hristo Abbey
The Kayı's warriors.
We'll take you back.
We won't leave you in the enemy's hands.
Get inside.
You all will be good Christians.
You heathens!
Our hearts are filled with faith!
We don't bow down.
Let's start with your look.
Behave, my good children.
Behave.
Don't worry. Osman Bey will save us.
He knows we are here.
I left tracks on the dungeon.
Don't let your eyes get wet.
We'll take Ahmed and our children
from their hands.
Don't worry.
You don't sharpen your sword
for nothing.
Of course, we will.
We'll take our children...
and their heads.
Be at ease.
May I enter, my bey?
Come.
I've talked to the women, my bey.
They are content.
They are praying in your name.
They await good news.
Soon.
They will reunite with their children.
May I enter, my bey?
Come, Cerkutay.
My bey, the Ahmed's marks
proved right.
They are in the abbey.
Mashallah.
Tell the mothers.
It's time they reunite with
their children.
Heathens finally touched
our children.
They are out of control, Davud Agha.
Out of control.
A great battle will take place.
We'll see.
Valiants show themselves
in battle.
Weapons, Gündüz Bey.
We need more weapons.
Davud Agha, if we fight
a great battle...
do you say that we don't
have enough weapons?
Not at all, my bey.
We have weapons.
But if you say a great battle,
weapons won't be enough.
We need more weapons.
You are right.
With the name of Allah.
We'll find a way.
We will.
Aya Yorgi Abbey
You won't change us.
The children are inside.
They are protecting them with
soldiers.
The place has two doors.
And both entrances are protected
by two soldiers each.
Five soldiers are patrolling the
yard.
When we break the gate and
get inside...
Turgut Bey, you will attack
the yard.
I sent Aykut earlier.
He'll let us know if there are
any soldiers other than the monks inside.
The rest will be dealt with by
our swords.
But don't forget that we have
children in there.
Remember that while using
your weapons.
Alps!
To the horses!
Osman!
Did you think that I would
give them to you that easily?
He couldn't get the kids.
Damn it!
Osman knows the location of
the kids!
You! Leave at once!
The children shouldn't be taken to
Hristo Abbey but to Aya Yorgi Abbey!
Move!
Soldiers! Get ready.
Nikola, Kosses and I...
will greet Osman.
But firstly, let's find some Turkish
clothing for the Christian kids.
Osman will think that they
are Turkish.
What are you waiting for?
You can't survive every ambush, Osman Bey.
It's over now!
Attack!
Archers!
To the hill!
Don't let them pass!
Come on!
What happened? Did you get
hunted in your hunt?
You will run away like this!
A wolf! You can't bite the lion!
But I must give it to him.
He cares about children.
He fell into the trap without
even thinking.
But he couldn't get the children.
The only thing he got is
a defeat!
Now...
we can visit the little Turks
in their new home!
Long live the Empire!
Aytekin?
My son...
Ahmed...
No...
My bey...
Our children...
Osman Bey, you subjugated the
whole world but...
you couldn't bring
our children back!
Don't you see?
They can't stand in our way
because of fear!
So that they go after our children!
With Allah's help,
Osman Bey will bring our children back!
Inshallah.
You are Kayı women!
Don't lower your heads!
Come on.
Come on, my girl.
We'll be strong.
Don't.
Come on.
O' my Allah!
Give me strenght...
to take my children back!
To the mothers
who are in pain...
I need to bring their
children back...
help me!
O' my Allah!
Answer my prayers!
Amin, my Allah!
You are my witness, Mother Selcan.
I wanted...
a baby, a child so eagerly.
Allah heard my prayers and gave him to me.
But where is my baby now? I can't live
without him, Mother Selcan.
Aya Yorgi Monastery
You know how to do this
very well, Rogatus.
You little monks.
You.
Tell me.
Which of the four gospels do
you like the most?
If you ask me, I'd prefer
the Gospel of Luke.
-What about you?
-Our book is one.
I don't worship what you worship.
If the reason for this arrogance
is Osman...
don't trust him that much.
I found the trace you left
in that dungeon.
We set a trap for Osman who
you love very much.
You are lying!
Osman is defeated, Alexander.
We defeated him.
Osman will never be able
to get the children.
But he returned from Nicaea with
a good agreement.
What does it matter? If Söğüt will be
on fire, what does it matter?
Exactly.
All of their trade resources, families
and traders are in Söğüt.
If Söğüt burns, none of those
agreements mean anything.
Before everything, Söğüt will be on fire.
It will burn in such a way that its flames
will be visible from Constantinople.
But it's not enough for it just to burn.
After Priest Gregorious has
done his duty...
we will be standing by to enter Söğüt
with our own soldiers.
Fire can rule everything.
We will rule Osman.
Now, if you will excuse me...
we have a very big fire to start.
I hope these little monks choose their
favorite gospel as soon as possible.
See you later.
We will take our children from
their hands sooner or later.
Is there any trace of that traitor...
who caused so much trouble?
There is nothing clear yet, my Bey.
But we have our eyes on Gökçe.
Like the fruit-bearing tree, of course,
our tribe will have also rotten fruits.
But before this rot gets to the root and
tree, it must be cut as soon as possible.
Find who hides the traitor as
soon as possible also.
Orhan misses his father.
The love for the child is a
beautiful...
thing, isn't it?
When so many people are
deprived of this...
it is forbidden for me to smell or kiss
Orhan...
without taking the children
of the Turks...
from the hands of those infidels.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
My Bey, Priest Gregorius wants to see you.
Let him come.
This way.
Welcome, Priest Gregorius.
I am very sorry for this terrible
event, Osman Bey.
We are pleased that...
you worry about our problems.
I'm ready to do everything that I can
to save the children.
I just wanted to say this.
Thank you.
But there is no need.
As you wish, Osman Bey.
But know that I'm ready to
help whenever you need me.
Thank you.
You can leave.
The Priest.
The Priest may come in handy as the
children are confined to the monastery.
Why didn't you want, Osman Bey?
We'll handle it by ourselves.
We'll handle it by ourselves so that we
can be a big fish.
I never trust the priests or monks when...
the lives of children are at stake.
We'll handle it by ourselves.
I'll learn where Rogatus took the
children.
We will take our children from their
hands before they get hurt.
Didn't Osman's behavior seem
strange to you too, Andreas?
I don't like how he turned down
our offer of help.
He was very affected by the
kidnapping of those children.
What if he suspects us?
What if he realized our purpose?
If that were the case, he
wouldn't have left us alive.
He would separate our
heads from our bodies.
But we will be careful no matter what.
The game in Söğüt will run smoothly.
And Osman won't know anything
until he sees the rising flames.
Aya Yorgi Monastery
My Allah.
I want Osman Bey to find us.
That's why I left a trace.
I wish I wouldn't do this.
Osman Bey has fallen into
a trap because of me.
Who will save us now?
My Almighty Allah.
I do not complain about any difficulties
that come to me from you.
But my brothers are innocent.
Osman Bey is innocent.
My Allah, we have no remedy
other than you.
We don't want help from
anyone other than you.
Destroy all the traps.
Save us from here.
Grant us to live by our faith.
Amen.
Weapons are my only talent.
Come on, play this qopuz.
May the souls of veterans rest in peace.
-Brother.
Come on.
Play the qopuz, brother.
Healing the wounds in our hearts...
is in your hands, brother.
Alright.
-Old Turkic song plays-
-lyrics are in old Turkic-
Bully for.
O traveler, where is your journey to?
To Kızılelma.
What is the range?
The death.
For whom do you yearn?
-For the Turkish land.
-Where is the Turkish land?
The whole world.
Let the whole world be your homeland.
May the world be good to you.
May your case be resulted in victory...
Osman Bey
Tell me what you heard from
Constantinople.
As you wish, I learned the details.
Rogatus wanted a priest from
Constantinople to educate the children.
The Priest is going to the Aya Yorgi
Monastery in Kökhisar.
The children are in there, Osman Bey.
They took them there not
only to hide them...
but to turn them from their way...
and to make Turkish children Christians.
But no one will be able to do this.
Does the priest come with...
a warrant or an edict?
Yes, Osman Bey.
Then prepare one for me too.
The Castle of Harmankaya.
You will be in Söğüt tomorrow, Samuel.
Take soldiers with you.
I don't want any mistakes this time.
Everything will proceed as we planned.
There will be neither error
nor mishap, sir.
Everything will be as you wanted.
Do you realize how strong we are when
we are together, my dear friend?
Of course.
No one can stand against such a power.
I want to strengthen this union
even more, Kosses.
Alliances, ranks and even friendships
are doomed to fall.
They are.
But...
But family.
Is it like that?
Family?
Family means...
being together for forever, Kosses.
I don't like beating around the bush.
I want to marry Mari.
Is that so?
There is no problem for me.
But what Mari thinks about this?
I will talk to her.
The children are in Aya Yorgi Monastery.
Then what are we waiting for my Bey?
Let's go and take our children.
We need to take precautions, Demirci.
Our enemies don't care about anything.
We need to be careful so that nothing
happens to the children.
What will we do, my Bey?
We will send a spy to the monastery.
I can go, my Bey.
They will realize who you are
from your weapon.
From your voice.
A priest is coming from Constantinople.
Someone should go to the
monastery instead of him.
How can we make it possible, my Bey?
Everyone in this camp has similar
features.
Moreover, whoever will go
needs to pretend as a priest.
You are right.
That's why it needs to be someone that...
doesn't arouse suspicion.
Who can it be, my Bey?
It is obvious who will do it.
He will be here soon.
Can I come in, Osman Bey?
Come.
You called me, my Bey.
Is this the best you can find, my Bey?
Brother, are you sure?
I have a duty for you.
Oh my.
Oh my, Osman Bey.
They are keeping our children in the
monastery.
For our children...
you need to wear this.
There is no role we can't play to
save our children, my Bey.
Aya Yorgi Monastery
Alexander.
This name suits you well.
Future warriors of Jesus Christ.
The monastery has been very good for you.
What is this?
You will not wear anything but the holy
cross...
will you, Alexander?
Get rid of this.
Let me help you.
You have no power to take this from me!
What did you do?! Brother!
What did you do?!
Take them out of my sight!
What did you do to him, huh?!
I don't know where these Turks'
stubbornness comes from.
But when they become good Christians
they will be of great use to me.
But first, they will learn not to resist.
I will discipline them all.
In the name of Allah.
My Allah.
The hearts are in your hands.
You know my faith and intention.
You are the forgiver.
Grant us to take our children from...
the hands of our enemies with your help.
Only fools carry the staff.
I am entrusting it to you until
I fulfill my duty.
I got it, Kumral Abdal.
Unfortunately, your fun years in the
emperor's city...
Constantinople are a thing of
the past, Mari.
Our lands are in danger.
We have to create a safe
and impassable line.
And unfortunately, we can't
achieve that with an alliance.
We need to be a family.
You know well that kindredship comes first.
What do you want to tell, brother?
Nicola.
He wants to marry you.
Yes, I was nice to him a few
times for our purposes.
But how can he find this
courage in himself?
He went beyond the limits. I hope you put
himself in his place.
It is you who is going beyond
the limits, Mari.
I have already approved this marriage.
You better prepare yourself as
soon as possible.
No.
I will never marry someone I don't want.
I can't waste my life because of your
political ambitions, brother!
Behave yourself, Mari. You are
going too far!
I am your brother.
You have lived freely until now, from now
on you will live for your family!
Never!
-You will marry!
-Never!
You will never make me do
something I don't want.
Can I come in, Malhun Hatun?
Come, Bahadır.
You can leave, Gökçe.
What did you hear or see? What is
Gökçe doing?
Apparently, she is hiding
something, Malhun Hatun.
Sometimes she is dissappearing.
I don't know where she is going.
You will know, Bahadır.
You will watch her closely.
You will know where she is going, who she
meets with and what she is doing.
I had this edict prepared for you so that
Rogatus will not suspect you.
It will be your key for entering
the monastery.
May Allah be with you.
Kumral Abdal, bring our children
to us as soon as possible.
We will be waiting for you here.
Go safely.
Don't worry. You gave the duty to most
appropriate man, my Bey.
My Bey, the real priest is coming.
Kumral Abdal is their guest.
And the real priest will be our guest.
Let's get on the horses.
Malhun Hatun is getting
suspicious more and more.
it was obvious that this would happen.
What will I do now?
Keep calm, Gökçe.
Would I ever let anything happen to you?
Go get your belongings, we will run away.
Where will we go?
Don't worry. I have prepared everything.
We can't stay here anymore.
If you don't want us to die, trust me.
How will we do this? What if
they come after us?
Let's get out of here first.
The rest is easy.
Thank you, brother Bahadır.
Come on. Go and get prepared.
Hurry up.
A priest can't enter this land
without permission.
It's obvious that you haven't got
permission from us.
Now, return to the place you came
from, to Constantinople.
My soldiers will accompany
you for a while.
Aya Yorgi Monastery
You must be the Priest Philip.
May the love of Almighty Jesus be
with you, Landlord Rogatus.
We were waiting for your arrival eagerly.
Why did the emperor send you alone?
A clergyman needs no protection.
What protect us is the prayers.
Which church have you been to before?
Church of St. Mary...
of Constantinople.
I will serve the Almighty Jesus Christ
here from now on.
Welcome.
Your experience seems to make
our job much easier.
The children that have come
are a bit rebellious.
It's the same as what Jesus Christ
saw walking around in the synagogues.
They must be confused and desolate
like herds without a shepherd.
Matthew, chapter 9, verse 36.
I have heard of your devotion to the
words of Jesus Christ, Landlord Rogatus.
It seems what I heard is true.
If you'll excuse me, I want to
see the children now.
Do what I do.
Monk, show him.
Let him make a cross until there are
no traces of his degenerate Turkishness.
Kneel!
We only kneel in the presence of Allah.
Didn't our religion forbid cruelty
to children?
Yes, his serene highness.
Blessed ones are the merciful people.
Because they will get mercy.
You must be the Priest Philip.
Yes.
I will take care of the children of
Jesus Christ from now on.
I would like to see how you deliver
the teachings of Jesus Christ.
Oh, my beautiful children.
You will be connected to the
Almighty Jesus Christ with love.
In time, Christian teachings will meet
in your memory.
What are you saying, Priest?!
Go and tell this to your own children.
Leave us alone.
Don't test my anger,
little mouse. Be obedient!
Every word is a pearl in our holy book.
It says there; "Salvation comes
only with patience."
Be happy with your hope
and endure adversities.
Devote yourself to prayers.
Let's not make our children exhausted.
It's enough for today.
My brothers, Osman Bey will save us.
Let's go, Bahadir.
I don't want to spend one more second here.
Let's go Gokce girl.
We are free, right?
We are, yes.
Hide Gokce girl.
Let's go.
Bahadir?
You need to die so that
I can live, Gokce.
So, our Monastery's fame is
all over Constantinople.
Yes.
Emperor is pleased.
If this goes on like that, we'll need another
Monastery in Bilecik, he says.
Because we'll teach Christianity
to all the Turkish children.
Do you really believe that those little
devils can settle down with love?
Jesus Christ's love shall fill your heart,
sister Julia.
Mercy is sharper than a sword.
It is so sharp that it can make one
love his enemy.
These children will love us
through our mercy.
By the way, I want you to manage the ritual
in the church in Bilecik...
...at Feast of the Annunciation.
Also, you'd recite verses from
John the Apostle.
I'd love to! Little time left to
Feast of the Annunciation.
But, Lord Rogatus...
I can recite verses from
John the Apostle later.
Because Gospel of Luke is recited
in Feast of the Annunciation.
God's lamb shall be with you.
Brothers...
...we'll get out of here...
...just like how Kumral Abdal said.
For Jesus Christ!
You are on foot all day for
these children...
who are the future of Christianity!
Without us, they would run away, father.
You are Jesus Christ's loyal servants.
But you are sinners.
So many!
I see the hell!
Don't you visit the church?
Father, we spend all our time
waiting here.
We can't even attend rituals
here.
Something must be done.
I can't watch you go to
hell like this.
I will bless you right here.
You'll be cleansed from
your sins.
Come here.
You too, my child.
Come.
Sit.
Close your eyes.
It will be like you are
baptized again.
You need to be tied to
each other first.
He is more knowledgeable than
any priest I know.
He influences you.
You are the loyal servants
of Jesus Christ.
Stay close, so that evil
can't pass through your friendship.
My God, our father and
your son Jesus Christ...
protect us from our friends' betrayals!
Breath.
Kayı's warriors!
May Allah bless you!
Thank Allah!
Mashallah!
Come on!
Osman Bey is waiting.
But...
why did he say 'God's sheep'?
He should've said Agnus Dei.
Why didn't he say it in Latin?
Priests say it in Latin.
And this priest is coming from
Constantinople.
Do you think that the priest
doesn't know Latin?
A priest with such knowledge
must know Latin.
Right?
Come on.
Where are you going, Priest Philip?
To feed my children, Lord Rogatus.
You shouldn't have bothered.
Education starts in the kitchen.
This is a pleasure for me.
I'm glad we have you, father.
Please, go on.
Soldiers?
Father?
Damn it! Soldiers!
Soldiers! Stop the priest!
Stop the priest!
Come on, Kumral Abdal.
Bring our valiants back.
My bey, inshallah Kumral Abdal
succeeds.
Göktuğ! Who do you think
Kumral Abdal is?
He was back to back with
Sarı Saltuk in many battles.
He disguises so well that...
even the heathens see him as
one of them.
Alright, my bey.
We'll get our children.
We won't leave them to the heathens!
Stop! Don't run!
Children.
Alps! Come on!
Come on!
Stop!
Alps!
Charge!
Osman Bey!
Osman!
-Come on!
-Osman Bey!
Hurry!
Hurry! Run!
My valiants!
Are you alright?
We didn't bow, my bey.
We showed them the Kayı!
Mashallah to my valiants!
My lions!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Give me the relic.
Oh, Kumral Abdal.
We are retreating!
I will kill you all!
Boran!
Are you alright, Kumral Abdal?
Thank Allah, my bey.
Mashallah!
Come on!
Boran, come on!
Boran!
I also feel the fire of Gonca
in me!
But we'll go for the children!
My bey.
Boran! Come on!
Alps!
I won't die before you, weasel!
I will come back for you!
I will return for you!
Let them go!
Let them!
Idiots!
Army of idiots!
You couldn't take care of a handful
of kids!
A handful of kids!
Why are you dying?
Idiots!
We couldn't take care of
a handful of kids!
Turgut Bey's Tribe
Are you out of strenght?
Are your knees weak?
Don't forget!
Your sword is a part of you.
You won't let it fall!
Come on. Take it.
You are sweaty!
But it's good. Those who sweat
the most in the training...
bleeds the least on the battlefield!
Come on.
It's enough for now.
Everyone to your jobs!
Remember what I said, alps!
Mari.
Won't you welcome me?
I'm surprised.
But of course, welcome.
I want to talk to you about something,
Turgut Bey.
Go on.
I'm listening.
If you are here for breaking the
agreement, it's long done.
Won't you invite me inside?
Sorry about that.
Come, let's get into the tent.
Hay Masha Allah(praise be) my Orhan.
Attaboy of his mother!
Can I come in?
Come Bahadır.
Bahadır?
What happened?
What happened to you?
I saw Gokce leaving the tent secretly.
- So?
- I followed her.
She met the soldiers of Lord in forest.
They talked a little.
The man gave her a pocket.
The soldier realized me at that time.
We fought.
I got Gokce, I wanted to take her to you.
She and the soldier united against me.
She run away with him..
- Malhun Hatun.
- Traitor!
Forgive me, my Hanim(lady).
I should have realised it earlier.
Gokce tricked us all.
However, you should have realised.
You are still bleeding.
Have your wound checked.
Gokce!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
(In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate).
You are not used to this,
Byzantine Beauty.
It's not like your dinner table.
Yes, you Turks are different.
So tell me.
What brought you here?
I wondered about you.
How has your arm been?
You know what happened at the castle.
And that the trade is over.
We are not friends anymore.
Why did you wonder?
Yes, I know it all, Turgut Bey.
What happens between you and my brother
doesn't interest me.
Also, there is a good cause
for all of this.
I agree...
Involving children is cruel.
That being said, infiltrating into the
castle to save the children...
is very brave.
No matter what is it about, Mari, ...
... I won't let anyone find peace if they
touche children.
Speaking of which, do you have a child?
Turks marry early as far as I know.
Haven't you married yet?
I was married.
Destiny...
My Hatun died...
...untimely.
Then I...
I didn't know.
I am sorry.
I was wondering about one more thing.
In your traditions, is a woman forced
to marry someone she doesn't want?
Never.
We first ask the woman if she wants him.
We don't force our Hatuns.
Why are you asking these?
I wondered.
To be honest...
My brother wants to marry me off to Nicola
without my will.
Why are you telling me this, Mari?
I should leave.
Thanks for dinner.
Can I come in, my Bey?
What are they asking for again, my Bey?
Mari's helper hasn't said a word either.
My Bey?
I don't know, Kutan.
I don't know.
She doesn't know what she wants.
And I don't either.
Argos!
It is time to hit the deathblow, Argos!
My soldiers... are my soldiers ready?
They are, sir!
I like vandalizing!
Osman!
Osman took the children, Nicola!
This is not important anymore,
my saint friend.
We'll burn Sogut down.
Those Greek Fires are everywhere in
mosques, khanqahs...
...bazaars, everywhere!
We'll burn Sogut down!
I want to take revenge on
Osman immediately!
We shall burn them down!
Let's not make Kosses wait.
Ahmet!
Mother!
- Ahmet!
- Mother Bala!
Ahmet! Ahmet!
Mother Bala!
My Ahmet.
Thank Allah!
Welcome!
My Ahmet.
- My Osman!
- Mother!
Mother.
- Welcome son.
- Thank you.
May Allah bless you my Bey!
- Bala.
- Osman.
Long live Osman Bey!
We found them thanks to my valiant!
Hay Masha Allah my lion!
You brought their sons to mothers.
You dashed their tears away.
Now you shall hug your child.
My Orhan.
Masha Allah (praise be).
Masha Allah my lion.
Infidels...
...exceeded their limits...
...intended to take our children away!
...Mothers...
...Fathers...
...cried a lot.
They hardened their heart!
Their aim was to change our children's
religion.
They wanted to vanish the love of
Allah and prophet.
However, they don't know that...
we have raised them with the names
of Allah and Quran...
... since their childhood!
They grew their faith inside!
Like a mighty plane tree.
A hard-rooted person...
...doesn't give up on their belief easily!
Not even by force of a sword!
Thanks to holy Allah first...
Then thanks to the wisdom of our children...
We overcame this trouble.
May my Allah bless my valiants!
Amin!
You don't mention yourself Osman Bey!
Our children are here thanks to you!
May Allah bless you my Bey!
It's beyond myself.
It's beyond Beyship.
It's beyond my life.
My life is in service of the Dawah!
Our road shall end in Kizilelma!
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Sogut.
Your words are lovely.
But this love is not in your holy book,
Sheik Edeali.
Your book says God loves only Muslims.
Do you know how we start doing
something, Gregor?
We start in the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Do you know what
rahman(merciful) means?
No, I don't.
Rahman is one of the finest
names of our holy creator.
That name describes his mercifulness
for all of the people.
That breath you take, Gregor...
...that eyes of yours...
...All of them are the reflection of
the name Rahman.
He gaves His blessings to everyone.
He doesn't differentiate.
But...
If one's heart is dark...
They ignore His blessings.
Your words are influencing,
my friend Edebalı.
Estagfirullah.
(Thanks).
If my words were influencing...
Sogut would be blooming.
My words doesn't come from me...
They come from the Rahman (merciful Allah).
We shall not take your precious time
any longer, my friend Edebali.
The doors of our heart and the doors
of our khanqah are always open to you.
My Bey!
They tried to deceive us by inviting us
to the dinner table!
But none of us ate!
We said we don't eat pork.
Masha Allah. Masha Allah!
The most beautiful halal prizes are
for the ones who don't touch haram, Ahmet.
So, my valiants.
Here we go.
I slaughtered a lamb for
the valiants of tent.
In the names of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Touching the banned is haram while
such food are available for you.
So, enjoy your meal!
Take it, my valiant.
Here we go.
How could you bear hunger...
...with your little body?
We bear with the power of faith.
Kumral Abdal told us about Hadrat Ali.
We drew ourselves up against the infidels
like him.
If I had a Zulfiqar (Ali's sword)...
imagine what I would do!
You didn't have a sword but you
stabbed the Lord with a fork!
Masha Allah my valiants!
Look at them!
As long as we have valiants like you...
...founding a state is close.
Let's eat.
Good luck with it, Davut Agha.
Your swords shall be sharp!
Who am I talking to?
I am forging a cross for you!
What are you talking about blacksmith?
Wait until you see it!
Ha! I told the tailor to prepare
a priest clothe for you.
My Allah, accept Abdal's prayers.
I am seeking for your help.
Give me patience.
My Kumral! You shall be patient.
Tell me.
How did they not realise you?
How did you save our children?
I learned leaving no track behind...
...from Saltug.
They didn't realise.
Masha Allah. Masha Allah.
After all, you'd make a good priest.
What did you say?
Nothing, nothing.
You are a skillful imitator...
...that's all I am saying.
You are Saltug's student, that's why.
My Kumral, may Allah bless you.
Mothers hugged their children
thanks to you.
Shut up!
I did nothing important.
Don't talk like that again.
Everything is done with the help of Allah.
We have countless crazies in our tribe!
Aygül Hatun.
Cerkutay.
Why do you not want me?
Is it because I am ugly?
No.
Then it must be because I eat too much.
Because I am crazy?
I am crazier than you.
Right.
Then why don't you want me, crazy girl?
Cerkutay.
You are a good man.
You are brave.
You are merciful.
You are manful.
But..
I am afraid to fall again.
I am afraid, Cerkutay.
Cerkutay won't fall!
I stand still.
I will not let you fall.
I will stand behind your back!
I won't fall even in an earthquake!
Also...
War is tougher than life.
You leaned on Cerkutay at war.
Why not now?
You'll come to me crazy girl!
Sshh!
I'll wait.
Cerkutay won't give up!
Also...
Love cannot be given up.
Sogut.
We placed the Greek Fire where
we wanted.
Sogut will burn down with our sign.
Excellent.
Sogut will burn down in their sleep.
Do not have doubt Priest Gregor.
Nothing sir.
Sogut will smell blood and ash tonight.
The disorder emerging after the explosion
will open the gates of Sogut for us.
We'll flare up the fire with our swords
before it extinguishes.
Osman took my village from me.
I will take everything from him.
The Christian community will welcome us.
When they see us, they will say...
Here are the real owners of Christianity!
Our saviors!
It's about to get dark.
Brave sons of Byzantine!
We'll end the domination of Turks in
this land!
For Jesus!
For Caesar!
For Jesus! For Caesar!
Sogut.
When they tried to kill Gregor...
I shielded him!
I made him responsible for the
Christian community.
However...
...however how can he...
...do such a betrayal,
how can he be such an evil my Sheik?
The goodness and the badness of
a human cannot be observed.
You can't see from outside.
Everyone does what they deserve,
Osman Bey.
Priest's grudge is revealed.
Eyvallah my sheik.
Akca Dervish.
Is it time?
Yes Osman Bey.
Damn it, why does it not explode?
Ignoble dog!
No one is around.
It's weird.
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey...
I beg you to forgive me.
For God's sake.
Akca Dervish...
...was after you like a shadow.
I know...
...every step you had,
every plan you had with Lords.
But this is not the only thing I know.
There's also your cruelty!
Even your religion can't purify you!
Those shops you intended to burn...
...were sinlesses'.
Those houses you intended to burn...
...were innocents'.
The mosque you intended to burn...
...is the house of Muslims!
But you...
don't deserve Hadrat Isah (Jesus).
You are not different from Judas Iscariot!
You even betray your people for
your desires!
As long as Turks exist...
...we will bring justice...
... with our swords!
This is such a sword that...
...always cuts the cruels!
Do you have anything to say?
Mercy...
Mercy, Osman Bey.
Mercy.
Mercy to the cruel...
...is betrayal to the oppressed!
Now take him...
...to his dear friend Rogatus.
And you shall not come to my land again!
My judgement is based on...
...Allah's justice.
Priest Gregor...
...intended to kill everyone including
Muslims and non-Muslims.
We don't consider the religion
of this betrayer!
We kill him even
if the betrayer is a Muslim.
I am Osman Bey,
the son of Ertugrul Ghazi.
I won't differentiate my people.
I treat them all the same.
I judge with justice!
We are pleased with your judgement,
Osman Bey!
Long live Osman Bey!
Until the whole world is Turks' land...
...we will continue facing the cruels!
Long Live Osman Bey!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com